<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FS Wallet</string>
    <string name="enterwalletmethods_str">Your first smart digital wallet</string>
    <string name="enterwalletmethods_createwallet">Create Wallet</string>
    <string name="enterwalletmethods_loadwallet">Import Wallet</string>
    <string name="walletname">Wallet Name</string>
    <string name="walletpassword">Password(At least 8 characterd)</string>
    <string name="confirmpassword">Repeat Password</string>
    <string name="passwordinfo">Password Hint（OPtional）</string>
    <string name="scan">Scan</string>
    <string name="paymentcode">receiving code</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="ReceiverAddress">Receiver\'s Address</string>
    <string name="dtv">Don\'t Transfer via Internet Tools</string>
    <string name="deleteWallet">Delete Wallet</string>
    <string name="managerwallet">Manage Wallets</string>
    <string name="transrecords">Transaction Records</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="changePassword">Change Password</string>
    <string name="exportPrivateKey">Export Private Key</string>
    <string name="exportKeystore">Export Keystore</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="simapleChinese">Simaple Chinese</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="aboutUs">About Us</string>
    <string name="currentVersion">current version:</string>
    <string name="checkUpdates">Check for updates</string>
    <string name="noUpdates">No updates available</string>
    <string name="assets">Assets</string>
    <string name="mnemonic">Mnemonic</string>
    <string name="official">Official</string>
    <string name="privateKey">Private Key</string>
    <string name="copyWalletAddress">Copy Wallet Address</string>
    <string name="transactionLog">Transaction Log</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="receive">Receive</string>
    <string name="balance">Balance</string>
    <string name="Amount">Amount</string>
    <string name="memo">Memo</string>
    <string name="miningFee">Mining Fee</string>
    <string name="slow">Slow</string>
    <string name="fast">Fast</string>
    <string name="advance">Advance</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="customGas">Custom Gas</string>
    <string name="customGasPrice">Custom Gas Price</string>
    <string name="data">data</string>
    <string name="howto">how-to</string>
    <string name="qrCode">QRCode</string>
    <string name="keystore">Keystore</string>
    <string name="copied">copied</string>
    <string name="from">From</string>
    <string name="to">To</string>
    <string name="gasFee">Gas Fee</string>
    <string name="copyUrl">Copy URL</string>
    <string name="transactionTime">Transaction Time</string>
    <string name="block">Block #:</string>
    <string name="transaction">Transaction #:</string>
    <string name="change">Change</string>
    <string name="currentPassword">Current Password</string>
    <string name="newPassword">New Password</string>
    <string name="repeatPassword">Repeat Password</string>
    <string name="l_import">Import</string>
    <string name="start_importing">Start Importing</string>
    <string name="copyKeystory">Copy Keystory</string>
    <string name="storeOffline">Store Offline</string>
    <string name="stp">Store to Password Vault</string>
    <string name="uia">Use in a safe environment</string>
    <string name="fds">For direct scanning only</string>
    <string name="mwa">Mnemonic words are separated by Spaces</string>
    <string name="fyl">Forget your wallet password? Import mnemonic or private key to reset the password.</string>
    <string name="gog">GasPrice or Gas cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="key_con">keystore content</string>
    <string name="key_pwd">keystore password</string>
    <string name="piy">Please input your private key </string>
    <string name="gas_cost">GAS costs</string>
    <string name="relevant_concepts">Relevant concepts</string>
    <string name="cap">Copy and paste the contents of the wallet keystore file directly to the input box, or scan the input by generating a qr code for the content of the keystore.</string>
    <string name="pca">Please copy and paste the keystore file to a safe, offline place to save. Do not save to mailbox, notepad, network disk, chat tools, etc., very dangerous.</string>
    <string name="fra">Friendly reminder: addresses are generally 42-bit characters starting with 0x</string>
    <string name="tad">This application does not store the password, has been unable to help you retrieve, please remember</string>
    <string name="pru">Passwords are used to protect private keys and transaction authorization, and strength is very important</string>
    <string name="trq">The qr code prohibits saving, taking screenshots and taking photos. It is only convenient for users to import wallets by direct scanning in a secure environment</string>
    <string name="iyl">If you need to store online, it is recommended to use password preservation software such as 1Password with higher security level to save the keystore</string>
    <string name="puw">Please use when nobody is around and there is no camera. Once the qr code is obtained by others, it will cause irreparable asset loss.</string>
    <string name="dnt">Do not transfer the keystore file through network tools. Once obtained by hackers, it will cause irreparable asset loss. It is recommended that the offline device be transmitted through two-dimensional code scanning.</string>
    <string name="applicationIntroduced">FS wallet is a mobile light wallet APP, which aims to provide ordinary users with a safe, simple, convenient and powerful digital asset wallet APP.</string>
    <string name="oapc">"On a public chain, anyone can read and write data. Reading data is free, but writing it to the public chain costs a fee that helps prevent junk content and protects it by paying. Any node on the network (each connected device containing a copy of the ledger is called a node) can participate in what is called mining to protect the network. Because mining requires computing power and electricity, the miners' services need to be paid for, and that's where the miners' money comes in. \n
        \nThe miners have the right priority to package gas, gas price high. If the user pays very low miners' fees, the deal may not be packaged by the miners, causing the deal to fail. \n
        \nTransaction fee of this wallet (also the transaction fee of ether fang) = gas quantity * gas price (gas unit price, ether currency)\n\n"</string>

    <string name="wig">"What is gas, what is gas price, and data? \n\n at ethereum, send tokens or call smart contracts, perform write operations on the blockchain, and pay miners to calculate the charges, which are calculated according to gas, which is paid by ETH. Whether the method you invoke succeeds or fails, there is a computational charge to pay. Even if it fails, the miner validates and executes your transaction, and must pay the miner's fee as if it were a successful transaction. Gas limit is simply how much gas a car needs to add. Gas price is the price per liter of gasoline. \n\ngas limit is called a limit because it is the maximum amount of gas you are willing to spend on a transaction. The gas required by the exchange is defined by how much code is executed by invoking the smart contract. If you don't want to spend too much gas, lowering the gas limit won't help much. Because you must include enough gas to pay for computing resources, otherwise gas doesn't report Out of gas enough. All unused gas will be returned to you at the end of the transfer. Therefore, send 1 ETH with imToken and set the gas limit to 400,000. After the transfer, you will receive 400,000-21000 gas returned. \n\n saves miners money by lowering gas price, but it also slows down their packing. If you want to speed up the transfer, you can set gas price higher so that you can get in line. If you don't hurry, you only need to set up a safe gas price, the miners will pack your trading check miners can accept the lowest gas price: http://ethgasstation.info/\n\nData is optional, used to invoke contract. You need to convert the corresponding string to hexadecimal, tool: http://string-functions.com/string-hex.aspx, fill in the hexadecimal data (start of 0x) such as makoshan to hexadecimal is 0x6d616b6f7368616e\n"</string>
</resources>
